[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":40342,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":53207,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</ sub>, yo u start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":5478,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":58689,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1642,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":60333,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3140,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":63474,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":2099,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":65576,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["6","0"],"rt":8817,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":74394,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1015,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":75410,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2613,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":78024,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1335,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":79361,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 o r bigger , you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2389,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":81752,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1024,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":82777,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2538,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":85316,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1021,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":86338,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":1978,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":88317,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":959,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":89277,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform + <sub>6</ sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3479,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":92757,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1046,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":93805,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":1983,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":95789,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1065,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":96855,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2068,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":98925,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1007,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":99934,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":13397,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":113333,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its  own inve rse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":29821,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":143155,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5559,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":148715,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1168,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":149885,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the  thing w hich you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3287,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":153174,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1015,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":154190,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2321,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":156513,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The  inverse  of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":827,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":157341,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2065,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":159407,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":921,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":160329,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember,  the inve rse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":6462,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":166792,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2978,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":169772,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":7371,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":177144,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last de finition  to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":40000,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":217145,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other e lement.) ","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":19609,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":236756,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1281,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":238039,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2237,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":240277,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under + <sub>6</ sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":2704,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":242983,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":4200,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":247184,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 =  4 +<sub> 6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1235,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":248421,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":4142,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":252564,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1170,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":253735,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4,  5, 6, 7 , 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":11452,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":265188,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2693,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":267882,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1001,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":268884,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3172,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":272057,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3030,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":275088,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3137,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":278227,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2180,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":280409,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2496,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":282906,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5.  I added 4 plus 1 and since it was not 9 or more I did not subtract 9.","response_history":["5.  I added 4 plus 1 and since it was not more t","5.  I added 4 plus 1 and since it was not more ","5.  I added 4 plus 1 and since it was not more","5.  I added 4 plus 1 and since it was not mor","5.  I added 4 plus 1 and since it was not mo","5.  I added 4 plus 1 and since it was not m","5.  I added 4 plus 1 and since it was not 0","5.  I added 4 plus 1 and since it was not 9 or more I  did not  subrt","5.  I added 4 plus 1 and since it was not 9 or more I did not subr","5.  I added 4 plus 1 and since it was not 9 or more I did not subtract 9."],"rt":26649,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":309556,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3.  I added 8 plus 4 and since it was 9 or more I subtracted 9.","response_history":["3.  I added 8 plus 4 and since it was 9 or more i","3.  I added 8 plus 4 and since it was 9 or more I subtracted 9."],"rt":17263,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":326820,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0.  When you combine  anythin g with zero you get that number back.","response_history":["0.  We","0.  When you combine anything with zero you get that number back."],"rt":49801,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":376622,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":6541,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":383164,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":2218,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":385383,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6.  When you combine 6 with 3 you get 0 back which means that is 6 is 3's inverse.","response_history":["6.  When you combine 6 with 3 you get zero","6.  When you combine 6 with 3 you get zer","6.  When you combine 6 with 3 you get ze","6.  When you combine 6 with 3 you get z","6.  When you combine 6 with 3 you get 0 back which means that is 6 is 3's inverse."],"rt":23993,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":409378,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes.  You can use 2+2 and so on to generate any number under +9.  For example 2+2+2+2 would equal 1.","response_history":["Yes.  Yi ","Yes.  Yi","Yes.  Yoy","Yes.  You can use 2+2+","Yes.  You can use 2+2","Yes.  You can use 2+2 and so on to generate any number under  base n","Yes.  You can use 2+2 and so on to generate any number under base ","Yes.  You can use 2+2 and so on to generate any number under base","Yes.  You can use 2+2 and so on to generate any number under bas","Yes.  You can use 2+2 and so on to generate any number under ba","Yes.  You can use 2+2 and so on to generate any number under b","Yes.  You can use 2+2 and so on to generate any number under ","Yes.  You can use 2+2 and so on to generate any number under +9.  Fr","Yes.  You can use 2+2 and so on to generate any number under +9.  Fore ","Yes.  You can use 2+2 and so on to generate any number under +9.  Fore","Yes.  You can use 2+2 and so on to generate any number under +9.  For example 2+9","Yes.  You can use 2+2 and so on to generate any number under +9.  For example 2+@","Yes.  You can use 2+2 and so on to generate any number under +9.  For example 2+2+2+2 would equal 1."],"rt":112430,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":521809,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No.  You can not you 3+3 and so on to generate any number.3+3 =6 but 3+3+3=0.  There is no way to get a number like 1 using 3 as a generator.","response_history":["No.  You can not you 3+3 ad","No.  You can not you 3+3 an ","No.  You can not you 3+3 and so on to generate any m","No.  You can not you 3+3 and so on to generate any number.3+3 = ","No.  You can not you 3+3 and so on to generate any number.3+3 =6 but 3+3+3=0.  THere is no","No.  You can not you 3+3 and so on to generate any number.3+3 =6 but 3+3+3=0.  There is not w","No.  You can not you 3+3 and so on to generate any number.3+3 =6 but 3+3+3=0.  There is not ","No.  You can not you 3+3 and so on to generate any number.3+3 =6 but 3+3+3=0.  There is not","No.  You can not you 3+3 and so on to generate any number.3+3  =6 but  3+3+3=0.  There is no way to get a number like one using ","No.  You can not you 3+3 and so on to generate any number.3+3 =6 but 3+3+3=0.  There is no way to get a number like o","No.  You can not you 3+3 and so on to generate any number.3+3 =6 but 3+3+3=0.  There is no way to get a number like 1 using 3 as a generator."],"rt":63563,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":585376,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No.  There is no way to get a number like 2 from using 5 as a generator.  5+5+5 would equal 3.  5+5 would equal 1.  ","response_history":["5+5","5+","5","No.  There is no way to get a number like 2 from using 5 as a generator.  5+5+5+5","No.  There is no way to get a number like 2 from using 5 as a generator.  5+5+5+","No.  There is no way to get a numbe r like 2  from using 5 as a generator.  5+5+5","No.  There is no way to get a number like 2 from using 5 as a generator.  5+5+5 wpi","No.  There is no way to get a number like 2 from using 5 as a generator.  5+5+5 wp","No.  There is no way to get a number like 2 from using 5 as a generator.  5+5+5 would equal 3.  %+5","No.  There is no way to get a number like 2 from using 5 as a generator.  5+5+5 would equal 3.  %+","No.  There is no way to get a number like 2 from using 5 as a generator.  5+5+5 would equal 3.  %","No.  There is no way to get a number like 2 from using 5 as a generator.  5+5+5 would equal 3.  5+5 would equal 1.  "],"rt":105207,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":690584,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No.  There is no way to get a number like 1 fro m using  6 as a generator. 6+6 = 3 and 6+6+6 = 9.","response_history":["No.  There is no way to get a number like 1 from using 5","No.  There is no way to get a number like 1 from using 6 as a generator. 6+6+6 =","No.  There is no way to get a number like 1 from using 6 as a generator. 6+6+6 ","No.  There is no way to get a number like 1 from using 6 as a generator. 6+6+6","No.  There is no way to get a number like 1 from using 6 as a generator. 6+6+","No.  There is no way to get a number like 1 from using 6 as a generator. 6+6 = 3 and 6=6=","No.  There is no way to get a number like 1 from using 6 as a generator. 6+6 = 3 and 6=6","No.  There is no way to get a number like 1 from using 6 as a generator. 6+6 = 3 and 6=","No.  There is no way to get a number like 1 from using 6 as a generator. 6+6 = 3 and 6+6+6 = 9."],"rt":74110,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":764695,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you  some qu estions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":12567,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":777263,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"The formula is 1 + n-1.","response_history":[" +n"," +"," ","1","The invers","The inver","The inve","The inv","The in","The i","The formula is 1 + n-1."],"rt":78338,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":855602,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you g ot your  answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"The formula is x+n-x.  I got this formula because to get the inverse you alway want to add the number that is equal to n minus the value of x.  For example if x = 2 and n=6 then the inverse of 2 would be 6-2 or 4.","response_history":["The foru","The for","The formula is x+n-x.  I got this formula because to get the inverse you alway want to add the number that is q","The formula is x+n-x.  I got this formula because to get the inverse you alway want to add the number that is euq","The formula is x+n-x.  I got this formula because to get the inverse you alway want to add the number that is eu","The formula is x+n-x.  I got this formula because to get the inverse you alway want to add the number that is eqal to ","The formula is x+n-x.  I got this formula because to get the inverse you alway want to add the number that is eqal to","The formula is x+n-x.  I got this formula because to ge t the in verse you alway want to add the number that is eqal t","The formula is x+n-x.  I got this formula because to get the inverse you alway want to add the number that is eqal ","The formula is x+n-x.  I got this formula because to get the inverse you alway want to add the number that is eqal","The formula is x+n-x.  I got this formula because to get the inverse you alway want to add the number that is eqaual to ","The formula is x+n-x.  I got this formula because to get the inverse you alway want to add the number that is eqaual to","The formula is x+n-x.  I got this formula because to get the inverse you alway want to add the number that is eqaual t","The formula is x+n-x.  I got this formula because to get the inverse you alway want to add the number that is eqaual ","The formula is x+n-x.  I got this formula because to get the inverse you alway want to add the number that is eqaual","The formula is x+n-x.  I got this formula because to get the inverse you alway want to add th e number  that is eqaua","The formula is x+n-x.  I got this formula because to get the inverse you alway want to add the number that is eqau","The formula is x+n-x.  I got this formula because to get the inverse you alway want to add the number that is eqa","The formula is x+n-x.  I got this formula because to get the inverse you alway want to add the number that is equal to n minus the value of x.  For example is ","The formula is x+n-x.  I got this formula because to get the inverse you alway want to add the number that is equal to n minus the value of x.  For example is","The formula is x+n-x.  I got this formula because to get the inverse you alway want to add the number that is equal to n minus the value of x.  For example if x = 6 and n=","The formula is x+n-x.  I got this formula because to get the inverse you alway want to add the number that is equal to n minus the value of x.  For example if x = 2 and n=6 the ","The formula is x+n-x.  I got this formula because to get the i nverse y ou alway want to add the number that is equal to n minus the value of x.  For example if x = 2 and n=6 then the inverse of x","The formula is x+n-x.  I got this formula because to get the inverse you alway want to add the number that is equal to n minus the value of x.  For example if x = 2 and n=6 then the inverse of 2 would be 6-2 or 4."],"rt":117960,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":973563,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I think that the pattern is that an element x is a generator if it is odd and n is equal or x is equal and n is odd.","response_history":["I think that the pattern is that a number is a n","I think that the pattern is that a number is a generator i s ","I t hink that the pattern is that a number is a generator is","I think that the pattern is that a number is a generator if it will ","I think that the pattern is that a number is a generator if x","I think that the pattern is that a number is a generator if it is odd","I think that the pattern is that a is a generator if it is odd","I think that the pattern is that an  is a generator if it is odd","I think that the pattern is that an e is a generator if it is odd","I think that the pattern is that an el is a generator if it is odd","I think that the pattern is that an ele is a generator if it is odd","I think that the pattern is that an elem is a generator if it is odd","I think that the pattern is that an eleme is a generator if it is odd","I think that the pattern is that an elemen is a generator if it is odd","I think that the pattern is that an element is a generator if it is odd","I think that the pattern is that an element  is a generator if it is odd","I think that the pa ttern is  that an element x is a generator if it is odd and n is equal or x is q","I think that the pattern is that an element x is a generator if it is odd and n is equal or x is eu","I think that the pattern is that an element x is a generator if it is odd and n is equal or x is equal an d","I think that the pattern is that an element x is a generator if it is odd and n is equal or x is equal an ","I think that the pattern is that an element x is a generator if it is odd and n is equal or x is equal and n is odd."],"rt":71201,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1044765,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":7188,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1051954,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0. 13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4784,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1056739,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":9717,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1066458,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"True.  If x is a  multipl e of n then it means that it won't be possible for you to generate odd numbers using only x.","response_history":["True.  If x is a ml","True.  If x is a multiple of nt ","True.  If x is a multiple of nt ","True.  If x is a multiple of nt","True.  If x is a multiple of n then it means that it won't pe","True.  If x is a multiple of n then it means that it won't p","True.  If x is a multiple of n then it means that it won't be possible for you to get ","True.  If x is a multiple of n then it means that it won't be possible for you to get","True.  If x is a multiple of n then it means that it won't be possible for you to ge","True.  If x is a multiple of n then it means that it won't be possible for you to g","True.  If x is a multiple of n then it means that it won't be possible for you to generate odd numbers using only x."],"rt":44022,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1110483,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an ele ment x i s a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":6292,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1116776,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"Never.  If x is added to itself it will become a number that is divisible by n and will therefore no longer be a generator.","response_history":["Sometimes.  I don","N.  I don","Ne.  I don","Neve.  I don","Never.  I don","Never.  If it ","Never.  If it","Never.  If i","Never.  If x is added to itself i t will b ecome a m","Never.  If x is added to itself it will become a number that is dvisable by","Never.  If x is added to itself it will become a number that is dvisable b","Never.  If x is added to itself it will become a number that is dvisable ","Never.  If x is added to itself it will become a number that is dvisable","Never.  If x is added to itself it will become a number that is dvisabl","Never.  If x is added to itself it will become a number that is dvisab","Never.  If x is added to itself it will become a number that is dvisa","Never.  If x is added to itself it will become a number that is dvisible by ","Never.  If x is added to itself it will become a number that is divisible by n and will therefore no longer be a generator."],"rt":104534,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1221313,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n< /sub> al ways, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":15242,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1236559,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":2056,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1238616,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"30","response_history":["30"],"rt":2848,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1241465,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some c ollege,  no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":3277,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1244742,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Advanced Calculus and Advanced Geometry.","response_history":["Advanced Calculus and Advanced Geometry."],"rt":17731,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1262475,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but  didn't  know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":6705,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1269181,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":3232,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1272414,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4278,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1276694,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4334,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1281030,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2731,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1283762,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":2548,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1286311,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":5076,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1291388,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No.","response_history":["No."],"rt":3006,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1294395,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No.","response_history":["No."],"rt":2820,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1297216,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"}]